/*
   15 Mayıs 2025 Perşembe10:25:35
   User: 
   Server: DESKTOP-AOAB716\SQLEXPRESS
   Database: ogrenciBilgileriVT
   Application: 
*/

'Ogrenci' table
- Unable to create index 'PK_Ogrenci'.  
The CREATE UNIQUE INDEX statement terminated because a duplicate key was found for the object name 'dbo.Ogrenci' and the index name 'PK_Ogrenci'. The duplicate key value is (257).
Could not create constraint or index. See previous errors.
The statement has been terminated.

